[Alarm beeping] Captain, external sensors just rebooted on their own.
CAPTAIN LIRA: That's not possible. We've had no power for days.
TECH RAN: The antenna array is transmitting… but not our frequency.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Patch it. Audio only. Be ready to cut it off.
[Distorted static] 'To anyone hearing this… we failed.'
TECH RAN: Captain, the voiceprint—it's you.
[Soft static] The rift glows like a bruise in space.
CAPTAIN LIRA: We hold position until we understand this.
TECH RAN: I'm seeing a carrier we don't own.
[Transmission] 'Stay away from the rift. It remembers.'
The rift outside flickers; we hold our breath.
We catalog anomalies and conserve power.
[Hull creaks] Micro‑fractures register on the skin.
CAPTAIN LIRA: No heroics. Discipline saves lives.
TECH RAN: Voiceprint analyzer is running.
[Ghostly echo] 'We were us, but not… entirely.'
The rift outside flickers; we hold our breath.
We catalog anomalies and conserve power.
[Console chirps] Power relays cycle in low‑power mode.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Patch it through. Audio only.
TECH RAN: Power grid is unstable but holding.
[Broken whisper] 'Timestamps don't match. Run.'
The rift outside flickers; we hold our breath.
We catalog anomalies and conserve power.
[Distant thud] Something brushes the outer hull.
CAPTAIN LIRA: I want redundancies on every critical bus.
TECH RAN: The rift's edge is shearing radio bands.
[Static-laced] 'Loop after loop. We forget, then repeat.'
The rift outside flickers; we hold our breath.
We catalog anomalies and conserve power.
[Air recycler hum] Condensation beads on the bulkhead.
CAPTAIN LIRA: If it's bait, we don't bite—yet.
TECH RAN: I'm throttling background processes to save juice.
[Fading] 'Whoever you are—cut power.'
The rift outside flickers; we hold our breath.
We catalog anomalies and conserve power.
[Alarm beeping] External sensors flicker to life.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Status report. Keep it tight.
TECH RAN: Antenna array is live, but it shouldn't be.
[Distorted voice] 'If anyone hears this… we failed.'
The rift outside flickers; we hold our breath.
We catalog anomalies and conserve power.
[Soft static] The rift glows like a bruise in space.
CAPTAIN LIRA: We hold position until we understand this.
TECH RAN: I'm seeing a carrier we don't own.
[Transmission] 'Stay away from the rift. It remembers.'
The rift outside flickers; we hold our breath.
We catalog anomalies and conserve power.
[Hull creaks] Micro‑fractures register on the skin.
CAPTAIN LIRA: No heroics. Discipline saves lives.
TECH RAN: Voiceprint analyzer is running.
[Ghostly echo] 'We were us, but not… entirely.'
The rift outside flickers; we hold our breath.
We catalog anomalies and conserve power.
[Console chirps] Power relays cycle in low‑power mode.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Patch it through. Audio only.
TECH RAN: Power grid is unstable but holding.
[Broken whisper] 'Timestamps don't match. Run.'
The rift outside flickers; we hold our breath.
We catalog anomalies and conserve power.
[Ship rumbling] Energy spike from the rift! We're being pulled in.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Stabilize the thrusters! Hold at twenty degrees pitch.
TECH RAN: The loop window repeats every fourteen minutes.
[Layered] 'We tried to fight. The rift learned us.'
Rift harmonics climb; time feels threaded.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[Gyros whine] Auto‑stabilizers fight the pull.
CAPTAIN LIRA: We break the loop by breaking the pattern.
TECH RAN: I'm tagging anomalies as 'us‑variants'.
[Hollow] 'Last chance is not a metaphor.'
Rift harmonics climb; time feels threaded.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[Ship rumbling] The rift swells like a tide.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Counter‑thrust twelve percent. Hold vector.
TECH RAN: Structural integrity at eighty‑two percent.
[Transmission returns] 'This is your echo. We didn't listen.'
Rift harmonics climb; time feels threaded.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[Lights flicker] Shadows stretch across the deck.
CAPTAIN LIRA: We treat that message as a warning, not an order.
TECH RAN: I'm seeing reflections—copies of our telemetry.
[Overlapping voices] 'Cut power or be folded.'
Rift harmonics climb; time feels threaded.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[Metal groan] Frames protest the strain.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Mark every loop artifact. We learn fast or we die.
TECH RAN: Voiceprint matches you, Captain. Perfectly.
TECH RAN: The rift is generating a recursive loop. We're seeing versions of us.
CAPTAIN LIRA: If we break the loop, we break the cycle of our destruction.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[Sparks] A panel pops, then dies.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Helm, trim pitch by two degrees.
TECH RAN: Energy spike building inside the rift.
[Urgent] 'Shut it down. Live in the dark.'
Rift harmonics climb; time feels threaded.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[Sensor ping] Echo returns from nowhere and everywhere.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Lock down nonessential compartments.
TECH RAN: The loop window repeats every fourteen minutes.
[Layered] 'We tried to fight. The rift learned us.'
Rift harmonics climb; time feels threaded.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[Gyros whine] Auto‑stabilizers fight the pull.
CAPTAIN LIRA: We break the loop by breaking the pattern.
TECH RAN: I'm tagging anomalies as 'us‑variants'.
[Hollow] 'Last chance is not a metaphor.'
Rift harmonics climb; time feels threaded.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[Ship rumbling] The rift swells like a tide.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Counter‑thrust twelve percent. Hold vector.
TECH RAN: Structural integrity at eighty‑two percent.
[Transmission returns] 'This is your echo. We didn't listen.'
Rift harmonics climb; time feels threaded.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[Lights flicker] Shadows stretch across the deck.
CAPTAIN LIRA: We treat that message as a warning, not an order.
TECH RAN: I'm seeing reflections—copies of our telemetry.
[Overlapping voices] 'Cut power or be folded.'
Rift harmonics climb; time feels threaded.
We map the loop, looking for a breaking point.
[New transmission] 'This is your last chance. Cut power to survive.'
CAPTAIN LIRA: Helm, kill thrust. Engineering, kill heat.
TECH RAN: Field collapse beginning. We might drift free.
[Echo breaks] 'We aren't you anymore.'
Darkness swallows our noise; the rift starves.
We ride the silence and wait for release.
[Rift thunders] Then narrows, like an eye closing.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Say it with me—discipline.
TECH RAN: I'm seeing the loop artifacts thin out.
[Static falls] 'Cycle ended.'
Darkness swallows our noise; the rift starves.
We ride the silence and wait for release.
[Panels die] Consoles go cold under our hands.
CAPTAIN LIRA: We will not be the message we heard.
TECH RAN: We're free‑drifting. Vectors are clean.
[Empty band] '—'
Darkness swallows our noise; the rift starves.
We ride the silence and wait for release.
[Silence] Only the hull ticks as it cools.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Prepare to ride it out in silence.
TECH RAN: The echo line is gone. No more repeats.
[No transmission] —
Darkness swallows our noise; the rift starves.
We ride the silence and wait for release.
[Deep silence] Systems coast in minimal draw.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Against protocol… we go dark. Now.
TECH RAN: Cutting main bus. Life support to passive.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Against every protocol… shut it all down. Now.
[Systems powering off] Ship entering dark mode. Rift field collapsing.
We ride the silence and wait for release.
[Manual switches click] Lights dim to red.
CAPTAIN LIRA: If the pattern feeds on us, we starve it.
TECH RAN: Dark mode engaged. Emissions near zero.
[Dying carrier] 'Silence is the new signal.'
Darkness swallows our noise; the rift starves.
We ride the silence and wait for release.
TECH RAN: Main bus is cold. Emissions near zero.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Helm, kill thrust. Engineering, kill heat.
TECH RAN: Field collapse beginning. We might drift free.
[Echo breaks] 'We aren't you anymore.'
Darkness swallows our noise; the rift starves.
We ride the silence and wait for release.
[Rift thunders] Then narrows, like an eye closing.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Say it with me—discipline.
TECH RAN: I'm seeing the loop artifacts thin out.
[Static falls] 'Cycle ended.'
Darkness swallows our noise; the rift starves.
We ride the silence and wait for release.
[Panels die] Consoles go cold under our hands.
TECH RAN: We're drifting free. The loop is gone. I think… we made it.
TECH RAN: We're free‑drifting. Vectors are clean.
[Empty band] '—'
Darkness swallows our noise; the rift starves.
We ride the silence and wait for release.
[Silence] Only the hull ticks as it cools.
CAPTAIN LIRA: Prepare to ride it out in silence.
TECH RAN: The echo line is gone. No more repeats.
[No transmission] —
CAPTAIN LIRA: Let this be the last signal we follow blindly.
[Fade out] End of transmission.